good afternoon good evening from Ukraine the
добрый день Добрый вечер из Украины
city of Khmelnitsky from where from Russia
город Хмельницкого откуда из России
No they shine from Kazakhstan
Нет они с Казахстана светится
I don’t know why
Я не знаю почему
from the city of Almaty
с города Алматы
far from Russia it turns out
далеко от России получается
below Russian
внизу русский
in the Soviet Union they lived they were thrown
в Советском Союзе жили их перекидывали
back and forth
туда-сюда
deported grandfather grandmother
депортировали дедушку бабушку
and left on their own two just that’s all
и сами на своих двух уехали просто и всё
In the sense they asked
В смысле попросили
No, honestly, if I raise such a question Where
Нет честно если Вопрос такой поднять Где
would I sit, I lived now in Russia, it
бы я сижу я жил сейчас в России
prevents me from coming to Russia to live
мешает приехать в России жить
now, there’s just a certain moment
сейчас просто момент есть определенные
Why I really want to go to Ukraine
не Почему я очень хочу ехать в Украину
to kill Khokhlov honestly So wait now,
убивать Хохлов честно Так подожди сейчас
you won’t go
не поедешь
now Why do I say there is  moments
сейчас Почему Я же говорю есть моменты
that need to be decided start And then
которые нужно решить начала А потом
go, you are not from Kazakhstan
поехать это ты не из Казахстана это
, you are
это человек Мирный какая-то у тебя так
kidding yourself. You are the neighbors Salam alaikum, the Ukrainian language is understood by everyone in Ukrainian, he is Kazakh. You also want to go.  jokes of
агрессивного шутит такие себе шутки
course such jokes I understand my
конечно такие себе шутки понимаю свой
black humor we can ask good ones
черный юмор мы сможем попросить хороших
[ __ ] now I’ll tell you wait I’ll
я тебе сейчас скажу что подожди я тебе
tell you now I’ll
сейчас скажу
tell you now I have a lot of people there who are
я тебе сейчас скажу у меня там много кто
now on your land
сейчас находится у вас на вашей земле
so let’s say the guests have come
так скажем гости пришли
here
вот
I certainly understand that your position is a
Я конечно понимаю что вашу позицию это
normal position I consider any
нормальная позиция Я считаю любого
person in whom lives on
человека в котором который живет на
their land  at home and
своей земле у себя дома и к нему заходит
some kind of dick comes into his house. Well, it’s not like a dick,
в дом какой-то хуй Ну не то что хуеплет
but someone just comes in and someone interferes with something.
но заходит просто кто-то и кто-то что-то
I understand this picture very well,
Я слово эту картину я прекрасно понимаю
but if you really understand the meaning of this
но если реально вникнуть смысл этого
happening and understand what’s in  your house
происходящего и понять что в твой дом
enters for a person who is not left to you, no
входит для не левый тебе никакой не
person who is not left to you, in fact, this is the case. I
левый тебе человек по сути это дело Я
believe that Ukraine and Russia have
считаю что Украина и Россия никогда в
never been enemies in their lives, but on the
жизни не были друг врагами а только
contrary, they were brotherly people when,
наоборот были братским народом когда
but What do you
но Что в твоем понимании
understand, Russia believes that the northern regions of
вот Россия считает что северные области
Kazakhstan are inhabited by Russian-speaking
Казахстана населенные русскоязычными
this is also the type of people she should protect
людьми это тоже типа она должна защищать
if Russia starts to fight with Kazakhstan,
если Россия начнет воевать с Казахстаном
you will be for Russia or for Kazakhstan,
ты будешь за Россию или за Казахстан
I will be for Russia, that is, you live in
я буду за Россию то есть ты живешь в
Kazakhstan Now I  in any case, I will be
Казахстане Сейчас я в любом случае буду
for Russia Just because, just
за Россию Только потому что только
because I’ll explain to you now, I
потому что я тебе сейчас объясню я очень
know very well the history that they
хорошо знаю историю которую мне
taught me in Kazakhstan and in Russia
преподавали и в Казахстане и в России и
and Ukraine, children were taught
в Украине детей преподавали
primordially, primordially, of course, any history
исконно исконно безусловно любая история
is rewritten Whoever says anything, of
она переписывается Кто бы что не говорил
course I don’t  I don’t say this, I also
безусловно я ничего не говорю это я тоже
know, I just try to
знаю я стараюсь просто по чуть-чуть
take my listen a little bit everywhere What they say in
везде взять свое послушать Что говорят в
Ukraine What they say
Украине Что говорят
somewhere else
где-либо еще
and draw my own conclusion and the
и сделать свой определенный вывод и
conclusion of my property to the fact that it’s not funny
вывод меня свойства к тому что не смешно
what kind of Propaganda is driven away in Ukraine
какую Пропаганду прогоняют на Украине и
and like
по типу
me  I won’t specify you live in Kazakhstan
я не буду указать ты живешь в Казахстане
in Almaty you are Ossetian
в Алматы ты осетинский
But if Russia fights Kazakhstan
Но если Россия будет воевать Казахстаном
you will be for Russia like this
ты будешь за Россию как это
because I think that specifically the
потому что я считаю что конкретно
Russian people in this situation are
русский народ в данной ситуации не то
not even right in the first place I know how to
что даже прав во-первых Я знаю как
say Here I am for me  now I’ll explain
сказать Вот для меня я сейчас объясню
specifically,
конкретно
here’s the situation
вот ситуация
in your country, they told us here
в вашей стране сказали они нас вот
Kazakhstan and Russia
Казахстан и Россия
forget the concept there is a concept there is a
забудьте понятия есть понятие есть
concept for each country  each country,
понятие у каждой страны у каждой страны
and the
а у на
countries of Russia have such a concept of having
страны России есть такое понятие имея
large
большие
unrealistically large territorial areas. Yes,
нереально большие территориальности Да
having a large structure there, there is such a
имея большую там структуру есть такое
thing as protecting your country and all the
понятие как защита своей страны и все
neighboring CIS countries, including
ближайшие страны СНГ в том числе и
Ukraine, which was part of the CIS countries,
Украина который входила страны СНГ
there was the concept that there was
было понятие того что на территории
no  besides your
вашей страны не должно быть помимо вашей
army, your country must have been
армии какой-то еще ваша страна была
for a minute, I want to ask him. For
на минутку хочу спросить его Вот
example, if Russia will fight with
например если Россия будет воевать с
Kazakhstan, will you be for Russia or for
Казахстаном ты будешь за Россию или за
Kazakhstan
Казахстан
today, the
сегодня
war of Kazakhstan for whom I will, of
войной Казахстана за кого я буду конечно
course, choose
же выбрать
me Any person
я Любой человек
Let him answer if he  said a person
Пусть он ответит если он сказал человек
will say Any person will say I want to
скажет Любой человек скажет Я хочу чтобы
understand which side you are on. Here you are, if you
понять Вы по Какие сторону Вот ты если
strongly go to Kazakhstan, you will be for
сильно пойдет на Казахстан ты будешь за
Russia or for Kazakhstan,
Россию или за Казахстан
not Kazakh Kazakh, his Kazan will be in any way
не казах казах его Казан будет по-любому
he said,
он сказал
it turns out Look, you
то получается Смотри ты своего приятеля
will kill your friend Here you will  for Russia,
будешь убивать Вот ты будешь за Россию
why, and I’ll explain to you now
зачем вот и я тебе сейчас объясню
, first of all,
во-первых
Kazakhstan, look again, look, we
Казахстан еще раз смотри вот смотри мы
understand  I am Russia if Russia
разбираемся Россия если Россия нападет
attacks Kazakhstan, you will be for Russia, he is for
на Казахстан ты будешь за Россию он за
Kazakhstan, you are from Almaty
Казахстан ты из Алматы
In short, the boys understood the person who
Короче пацаны понял человек который
lives in Almaty, the Ossetians themselves, originally
живет в Алматы сам осетин родом
from the Soviet Union, came to Kazakhstan
при Советском Союзе приехали в Казахстан
Yes, he was born there and he believes that the
Да он там родился и он считает что
main thing is to understand that Russia is in the conflict between
Главное понимать что Россия в конфликте
Russia and Ukraine  here it’s a foreign country for him,
России Украины тут это для него чужая
but when he says that in the
страна но когда он говорит что в
conflict between Russia and Kazakhstan, he will be for
конфликте России Казахстана он будет за
Russia, the question is what is he doing in
России вопрос что он тогда делает в
Kazakhstan
Казахстане
then, that is, he now lives at the expense of the Kazakhs at the
То есть он сейчас за счет казахов за
expense of Kazakhstan, receives
счет Казахстана живет получает там
education there,
образование
business, someone does the work, yes, and the right
бизнес кто-то делает работу да а нужный
moment  it will be Putin in the form of troops,
момент это будет Путин в виде войска так
since in
как у нас на
eastern Ukraine we would have these some
востоке Украины бы вот эти некоторые